[PHONE RINGING]
- Answer the phone, Leonard.
- No.
[PHONE CHIMING]
There. It went to voicemail.
(Sheldon:)Aren't you going
to check your messages?
(Leonard:)- No.
- You have to check your messages.
(Sheldon:)The leaving of a message
is one half of a social contract...
(Sheldon:)...which is completed
by the checking of the message.
(Sheldon:)If that contract breaks down,
then all social contracts break down.
(Sheldon:)And we descend into anarchy.
(Leonard:)It must be hell inside your head.
(Sheldon:)At times.
(Howard:)Guys, we have a code red.
Code red, the hospital emergency alert?
The computer worm?
Or the cherry-flavored soft drink
from the makers of Mountain Dew?
(Howard:)I was going over the schematics
on my Zero-G Toilet...